[
	{
		"num":"1",
		"question":"1. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"2",
		"question":"2. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"3",
		"question":"3. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"4",
		"question":"4. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"5",
		"question":"5. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"6",
		"question":"6. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"7",
		"question":"7. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"8",
		"question":"8. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"9",
		"question":"9. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"10",
		"question":"10. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"11",
		"question":"11. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"12",
		"question":"12. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"13",
		"question":"13. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"14",
		"question":"14. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"15",
		"question":"15. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"16",
		"question":"16. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"17",
		"question":"17. 17,19,23,29,31,37___",
		"option1":"47",
		"option2":"48",
		"option3":"41",
		"option4":"46",
		"answer":"41"
	},
	{
		"num":"18",
		"question":"18. 2,5,10,17,___",
		"option1":"24",
		"option2":"26",
		"option3":"20",
		"option4":"29",
		"answer":"26"
	},
	{
		"num":"19",
		"question":"19. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	},
	{
		"num":"20",
		"question":"20. 1,3,9,27__",
		"option1":"36",
		"option2":"81",
		"option3":"90",
		"option4":"78",
		"answer":"81"
	}
]

